AoM Publications 5289 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XII: Conflict Management Division, 1987-2007
  - Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 26: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 27: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Conflict Management Newsletter, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 2: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 3: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
      By Academy of Management. May 1992. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 5: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 6: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 7: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 8: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 9: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 10: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 11: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Conflict Management Newsletter, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 2: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 3: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 4: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 5: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 6: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 7: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 8: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 9: The Conflict Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 10: Conflic Management Division Fall 1995 Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 11: Conflict Management Division Fall 1995 Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 12: Conflict Management Division, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 13: Conflict Management Division Spring 1996 Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 14: Conflict Management Division Spring 1996 Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 15: Conflict Management Division Spring 1996 Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 16: Conflict Management Division Fall 1996 Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 17: Conflict Management Division Fall 1996 Newslette, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 18: Conflict Management Division Fall 1996 Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 19: Spring 1997 Newslette, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
      By Academy of Management. Item is in English.
    - Item 20: Spring 1997 Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 21: Spring 1997 Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 22: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 23: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 24: 1998 Academy of Management Meetings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
      By Academy of Management. August 9-12, 1998. Item is in English.
    - Item 25: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 26: 1998 Academy of Management Meetings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 27: 1998 Academy of Management Meetings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Conflict Management Newsletter, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: 18th Annual International Conference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
      By Strategic Management Society. November 1-4, 1998. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: 18th Annual International Conference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 3: 18th Annual International Conference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 4: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
      By The Academy of Management. Spring 1998. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
      By The Academy of Management. Fall 1998. Item is in English.
    - Item 6: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 7: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 8: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
      By The Academy of Management. Spring 1999. Item is in English.
    - Item 9: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 10: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 11: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
      By The Academy of Management. Spring 2000. Item is in English.
  - Conflict Management Newsletter, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 2003. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Item 3: Conflict Management Division Newslette, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Item 4: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 2001. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Item 6: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Conflict Management Newsletter, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 2004. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 3: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 4: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 2004. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 6: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 7: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
      By Academy of Management. Summer 2005. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 9: Conflict Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Conflict Management Division Newsletter, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Conflict Management Division Newsletter, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Series XIII: Eastern Academy of Management, 1990-2003
  - EAM Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - EAM Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - EAM Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - EAM Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - EAM Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - EAM Annual Meeting, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Call for Papers, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - EAM Annual Meeting, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - EAM Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - EAM Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - EAM Annual Meeting, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Meeting Notes, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Technology in the Wild, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Series XIV: Entrepreneurship Division, 1990-2007
  - Entrepreneurship Newsletter, 1990-1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
      By Academy of Management. Vol 5, No 1. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
      By Academy of Management. May 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 4: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 5: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 6: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
      By Academy of Management. Summer 1996. Item is in English.
    - Item 7: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 8: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 9: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 10: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 11: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 12: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
      By Academy of Management. Summer 1998. Item is in English.
    - Item 13: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 14: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 15: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 16: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
      By Academy of Managementq. Fall 1998. Item is in English.
    - Item 17: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
      By Columbia Business School. Spring 1997. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
      By Columbia Business School. Spring 2000. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 4: Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
      By Columbia Business School. Fall 2000. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Entrepreneurship Newsletter, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
      By Academy of Management. Summer 1999. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 3: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 4: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1999. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 6: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 7: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
      By Academy of Management. Summer 2000. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 9: Entrepreneurship Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 10: 1999 Entrepreneurship Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
      By Academy of Management. Letter, Questionare. Item is in English.
    - Item 11: 1999 Entrepreneurship Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
      By Academy of Management. Letter, Questoinare. Item is in English.
    - Item 12: 1999 Entrepreneurship Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
      By Academy of Management. Letter, Questionarre. Item is in English.
    - Item 13: 1999 Entrepreneurship Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 14: Innovation in Entrepreneurship Pedagogy Award, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 15: Innovation in Entrepreneurship Pedagogy Award, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 16: Innovation in Entrepreneurship Pedagogy Award, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 17: Innovation in Entrepreneurship Pedagogy Award, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 2: Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
      By Columbia Business School. Spring 2001. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 4: Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - New England Journal of Entrepreneurship, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: New England Journal of Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
      By College of Business, Sacred Heart University. Spring 2003. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: New Englang Journal of Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Item 3: New England Journal of Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Item 4: New England Journal of Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
      By College of Business, Sacred Heart University. Fall 2003. Item is in English.
  - New England Journal of Entrepreneurship, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: New England Journal of Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 2: New England Journal of Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 3: New England Journal of Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
      By College of Business, Sacred Heart University. Spring 2004. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: New England Journal of Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 5: New England Journal of Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Entrepreneurship Newsletter, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Entrepreneurship Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 2: Entrepreneurship Division, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 3: Entrepreneurship Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
      By Academy of Management. 2004. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Entrepreneurship Division June Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 5: Entrepreneurship Division June Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 6: Entrepreneurship Division June Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 7: Entrepreneurship Division July Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 8: Entrepreneurship Division July Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 9: Entrepreneurship Division July Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 10: Entrepreneurship Division August Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 11: Entrepreneurship Division August Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 12: Entrepreneurship Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 2005. Item is in English.
    - Item 13: Entrepreneurship Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 14: Entrepreneurship Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 15: Entrepreneurship Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 16: Entrepreneurship Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 17: Entrepreneurship Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
      By Columbia Business School. Summer 2005. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Columbia Entrepreneurship Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Updates from the Entrepreneurship Division, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Eugene M. Lang Center for Entrepreneurship at Columbia Business School (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
      By Columbia Business School. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Item 3: Entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Darden School of Business Administration: Batten Briefings, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Series XV: Fellows Group of the Academy of Management, 2001-2006
  - Membership Directory and Handbook, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Programs, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Technology and Innovation Management Division: TIM Division List Serve, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Series XVI: Gender and Diversity in Organizations Division, 1981-2011
  Was formerly the Women in Management Division
  - Women in Management Newsletter, 1981-1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: The Academy of Management Women in Management! Interest Group Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. October 1981. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: The Academy of Management Women in Management Interest Group Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. March 1982. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: The Academy of Management Women in Management Interest Group Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. July 1982. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: The Academy of Management Women In Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 5: The Academy of Management Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 6: The Academy of Management Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. Summer 1983. Item is in English.
    - Item 7: The Academy of Management Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 8: Academy of Management Women in Management Interest Group Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. October 1983. Item is in English.
    - Item 9: The Academy of Management Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. Winter 1983. Item is in English.
    - Item 10: Academy of Management Women in Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. February 1984. Item is in English.
    - Item 11: Academy of Management Women in Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. June 1984. Item is in English.
    - Item 12: Academy of Management Women in Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. October 1984. Item is in English.
    - Item 13: Academy of Management Women in Management Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. February 1985. Item is in English.
    - Item 14: Academy of Management Women In Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. June 1985. Item is in English.
    - Item 15: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1985. Item is in English.
    - Item 16: Women In Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. Summer 1986. Item is in English.
    - Item 17: Women In Management, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1986. Item is in English.
    - Item 18: Women In Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. Winter 1986. Item is in English.
    - Item 19: Women In Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 20: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 21: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 22: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 23: Women In Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1987. Item is in English.
    - Item 24: Women In Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 25: Women In Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 26: Women In Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. Summer 1988. Item is in English.
  - Women in Management Newsletter, 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
      By Academy of Management, Women in Management. October 1988. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 3: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
      By Academy of Management, Women in Management. Spring 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 5: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 6: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
      By Academy of Management, Women in Management. Fall 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 7: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 8: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 9: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
      By Academy of Management, Women in Management. Winter 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 10: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 11: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 12: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
      By Academy of Management, Women in Management. Spring 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 13: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 14: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 15: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 16: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 17: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
      By Academy of Management, Women in Management. Winter 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 18: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
      By Academy of Management, Women in Management. Spring 1991. Item is in English.
    - Item 19: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 20: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 21: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
      By Academy of Management, Women in Management. Fall 1991. Item is in English.
    - Item 22: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 23: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 24: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
      By Academy of Management, Women in Management. Winter 1991. Item is in English.
    - Item 25: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 26: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 27: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
      By Academy of Management, Women in Management. Spring 1992. Item is in English.
    - Item 28: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 29: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Women in Management Newsletter, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 2: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 3: Women In Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 4: Women In Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
      By Academy of Management. Winter 1992. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 6: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 7: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 8: Women in Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)